<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>states on International Law Corpus</title>
    <link>/tags/states/</link>
    <description>Recent content in states on International Law Corpus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/states/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>States in Clunet articles</title>
      <link>/posts/states-in-articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/states-in-articles/</guid>
      <description>This chart counts references to selected states the standalone articles in Clunet. The pattern seems to differ from the pattern in jurisprudence. Egypt is less prominent, while the Ottomans and Russia are more prominent. China, Greece, and Japan show a few outlying points, most produced by a single article focused on that state.
If we look at the pattern of occurence of the same words in the test of the jurisprudence bulletins themselves, we notice that the Ottoman empire and Turkey are less prominent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Counting states in jurisprudence reports</title>
      <link>/posts/jurisprudence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/jurisprudence/</guid>
      <description>The “Jurisprudence” section of Clunet contains thousands of “bulletins” reporting decisions. The section is subdivided by state. This scatterplot captures the number of bulletins for each state and their average length.
Number of bulletins is one proxy for the notability of a state. Of course, not all of these states were present throughout the sixty-five year period. I’ll break out time series in future graphs.
Length of bulletin is one proxy for the depth of engagement with jurisprudence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>